# JIN KUAN MOO

https://minahhh666.github.io/ https://www.linkedin.com/in/jin-kuan-moo/

# Summary

A UCD Computer Science Master proficient in Chinese Mandarin, English, and Malay. Full stack development experience in several languages as well as Agile methodology. Great networking (TCP/IP), OS (Windows, Linux) and machine learning knowledge. Previously worked as a manufacturing manager, leading a team of 20 engaged in daily production. Volunteered in Code in Place hosted by Stanford University, delivering online Python lessons to a group of 15 students. An excellent team player with great team management and communications skills.

Email: jkmoo0412@hotmail.com

Mobile: 0892059402

#### **Education**

**University College Dublin** Dublin, Ireland MSc Computer Science; GPA:3.82 Sep 2022 – Dec 2023

**University College Dublin** Dublin, Ireland BSc Food Science; GPA:3.77 Sep 2017 – Jun 2021

# **Experience**

Dublin, Ireland **Stanford University** Section Leader Apr 2023 – Jun 2023

• Participating in Code in Place, an online introductory coding course

• Conducting weekly lessons for a cohort of 15 students

• Teaching topics including Python, Animations, Console Programming, Graphic Programming etc.

Krispy Kreme Kildare, Ireland Sep 2021 – Jun 2022

Manufacturing Manager

- Managing a 20-member team for daily production operations
- Ensuring adherence to safety protocols, HACCP principles, and legal regulations
- Maintaining accurate inventory control, yield records, and traceability documents

## **Projects**

### **Afterparty**

an event impact analysis tool which provides insights into how the busyness of urban areas are impacted by largescale event.

- Utilized React.js and Figma for the frontend development
- Implemented the backend with Node.js, Express.js, Flask, and Apache
- Developed prediction models using Random Forest and XGBoost

## **Dublin Bikes**

a web application providing real-time information and journey planning for bike-sharing services.

- Utilized Vanilla JS, HTML and CSS for frontend development
- Implemented the backend with Flask, MySQL, AWS EC2, AWS RDS, Gunicorn, Nginx
- Developed prediction models using Linear Regression

### **Asteroids**

a classic arcade video game which player controls a spaceship in an asteroid field to destroy incoming asteroids.

- Developed using Java
- Used JavaFX as the GUI framework

### **Technical Skills**

- Programming languages: Python, JavaScript, Java, HTML, CSS, C++, TypeScript
- Frameworks: React.js, Flask, Express.js, JavaFX, Pygame
- Database: MySQL, AWS RDS
- OS: Linux, Windows, AWS EC2
- Tools: VSCode, Jupyter Notebook, Eclipse, GitHub, scikit-learn, Scene Builder, Microsoft Office
- Machine Learning: Linear Regression, Logistic Regression, Random Forest, XGBoost, KNN
- Others: Data Structures and Algorithms, Object-Oriented Programming, Networking (TCP/IP)